

#### ABOUT ME

My Name is Habibullah khan .I am student of hira foundation . Now doing o 'level and also a

Student of Aptech . Allhamdullaih I have some experience in IOT and robotics I am citified from autocon, TechZone and having a experience in marketing I have work about 2 years in Saleema collections. Allhamdulliah I have many of other skills and having a ability to learn, teach and managing I have work on many different projects. If you will hire me inshAllah I will perform better and fulfills your requirement

# Education

School && Institute

"O'Levels" from Hira foundation with computer

Software engineering certified diploma through "Aptech"

And now still studying

# M. Habibullah khan

Pakistan, Karachi, Shah Faisal colony 5 A#35, GA 75200 Phone: + (92) 318 1133107 Email: habibullahk728@gmail.com

# Experience

MARKETING (2018 - Now)

Software Engineering (2018 - Now)

The action or business of promoting and selling products or services, including market research and advertising

Software engineering is defined as a process of analysing user requirements and then designing, building, and testing software application which will satisfy those requirements.

SALES MANAGER (2020 - 2021)

Company = (Saleema collection)

In laces department I have experience of selling manager

Software House (no experience)

I have made and work in different projects

Like: (fanOfan) (Cepiall) and many of portfolio

### Skills

Frontend	Backend	Robotics	Projects
HTML5	PHP	Arduino	Portfolio
Bootstrap4	LARAVEL	Blynk	Ecommerce
java script	C &c#	grbl	Basic more

